Wiktor Ślęczka

(+48) 886-344-977 • wiktor.sleczka@gmail.com • Warsaw, PL

Programming Languages

Python Typescript *** C++ Bash **★**★☆ **★**★☆ Haskell **★**★☆ Matlab * \$ \$ Go ★☆☆

Git *** Vue **★**★☆ React Linux system **★**★☆ Docker HTML & CSS **★**★☆ **★**★☆ Flask PostgreSQL **★**★☆ Cherrypy ★☆☆ MongoDB ***

Other skills

English language Technical documentation reading and writing **Driving license** MS Office

Twitter: @wikii122 Github: github.com/wikii122 Stackoverflow: stackoverflow.com/users/ 2083998

Strong sides

Flexible Conscientious Quick learner Enjoys a challenge Works well without supervision

Profile

I worked on projects from many fields in the industry, ranging from automatics and robotics, through web and game development, up to big data and artificial intelligence. I'm also interested in information security and web technologies.

Above all, I enjoy challenging problems, but I also believe in minimalism and simplicity of solution. Therefore, for me usually it's not enough to solve the problem, but to solve it in the most clean and elegant way.

Experience

Fullstack developer, RTB House

September 2018 → Present

Part of the team responsible for presentation and processing statistics and settings.

Fullstack developer, Dealavo

May 2018 → August 2018

New features development and product maintainance for both frontend and backend.

Developer, cartonik.pl

February 2017 → May 2018

Design and implementation store's web stack, administration and maintenance of accompanying toolset.

Developer / Technical Founder, Scanye

November 2014 → July 2015

Design and implementation of initial product.

Full Stack Developer / Technical Founder, Appartment

May 2013 → February 2014

Design and implementation of front and backend for web application.

Intern, Samsung R&D Poland

June 2013 → October 2013

I was taking also occasional freelance jobs since 2011. Few examples of such work may be found on wiktorsleczka.com.

Education

The Faculty of Electronics and Information Technology, Warsaw University of Technology

2018 - Graduated M.Eng in Automatics and Robotics

2015 - Graduated B.Eng. in Computer Science